威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们要执行代码了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We're
about to execute code.
我说过执行代码有两件事。
I said there's two things
to executing code.
两部分，一部分，按照给定的代码，一行一行地检查，然后执行。
Two parts to it, one, going through the
code as given, line by line, and doing it.
第二，有一个可以看到数据的地方。
Two, having a place to see
stuff that shows up, data.
这正是运行代码所需要的。
That is literally what
it takes to run code.
正在运行的函数就像一个迷你程序。
A function being run is
like a mini program.
像一个迷你应用程序，像一些代码运行，因此，我们需要这两个东西。
Like a mini-app, like it's some code to
run therefore, we need those two things.
执行线程，一行一行地执行代码的能力。
The thread of execution, the ability to go
through the code line-by-line and do it.
还有一点数据存储,
And a little store of data,
存储器，用来存储我们在这个函数中出现的任何东西。
the memory, to store anything that shows
up while we're inside that function.
任何函数、变量、常量只能存储在那个函数中。
Any functions, variables,
constant stored inside that function only.
这两件事加在一起有一个非常，非常深刻的名字。
Those two things together have a very,
very profound sounding name.
有人知道吗？
Does anybody happen to know?
如果我把手臂这样举起来，那该叫什么呢？
If I put my arms up like this,
what that might be called?
一个全新的演讲者2: 执行竞赛。
A brand new
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution contest.
威尔 · 森特斯: 天啊，如果人们第一次看到这个,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: My, okay if people
are watching this the very first time,
第一次见面的时候，他们会说，好吧。
this first encounter, they're like, okay.
好的，没错，一个执行上下文。
All right, exactly, an execution context.
这是完全正确的人。
That is exactly right people.
创建来运行一个函数的代码，有两个部分，我们已经看到了。
Created to run the code of a function,
has two parts, we've seen them already.
执行线程，因为我们现在要去
Thread of execution because
we're now gonna be going
通过乘以两个行和一个内存的代码,
through the code of multiplied by
two line by line and a memory,
一个小空间来存储数据和函数，以便在函数内部声明。
a little space to store data and functions
to get declared inside that function.
所以这是正确的，在我们能够继续前进之前，跑步乘以2
So that's right for running multiplied by
two before we're able to move on to any
进一步的代码，我们要创建一个全新的执行环境。
further code, we're gonna create
a brand new execution context.
在这里，我要画一个大盒子。
Here it is, I'm gonna draw the big box.
看看这个，就是这个。
Look at this, this is what it is.
顺便说一句，我们已经看到一个了。
We, by the way, see one already.
这是个大问题，这个叫做全球问题。
This was the big one,
this is called the global one.
这是一个一旦我们开始运行我们的代码文件，我们创建什么’
This is the one that as soon as we start
running our file of code, we create what's
称为全局执行上下文，用于运行整个代码文件。
called a global execution context for
running the overall file of code.
那东西是主程序。
That thing is the main program.
一旦我们开始运行一个小函数，一小段代码,
As soon as we start running a little
function, a little mini bit of code,
我们创建一个迷你程序，一个迷你执行环境。
we create a mini program,
a mini execution context.
就是这个，我把它做得很大。
Here it is, I've made this very big.
就是这样，正如我所说，它分为两部分。
There it is, and
it has as I say, two parts.
第一，记忆,
One, the memory,
一个用来存放被申报在里面的东西的地方。
a place to store things that get
declared inside multiplied by two.
我们称之为本地记忆，因为它只是，本地的意思是附近。
We call it the local memory because
it's just, local means nearby.
只是在我们运行代码的时候可以使用的东西
It's just stuff that's gonna be available
while we're running the code and
再乘以二，这里没有。
multiply it by two,
not available out here.
任何我们在这个函数中宣布或声明的东西，任何
And anything which we announce or declare
inside this function, any variable for
明白了吗？
it, you got it?
存在这里，而不是这里，好吧。
Stored in here, not in here, all right.
在这个函数中
So, into this function we go and
我们在里面要做的第一件事是什么？
what is the first thing that
we're going to do inside of here?
伊森，我们进去第一件事要做什么？
Ethan, what is the first
thing we're gonna do inside?
伊森: 声明第一个结果。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Declare the const result.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 伊桑几乎是对的，这是我们要做的第二件事。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Ethan's almost right,
that's the second thing we're going to do.
但是 Ethan 只要我们在函数中运行代码,
But Ethan,
whenever we run code in a function,
我们处理 Ethan 的第一件事是什么？
the first thing we always
handle Ethan is what?
在我们触及身体我们处理的功能之前，我们得到了一些东西
Before we hit the body the function we
handle, we've got some stuff with sort of
插入到本地内存中的函数中。
inserting into the function that's going
to show up inside the local memory.
那是什么？
And that is?
伊森: 那么输入号码。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: So input number.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太好了。 会被设置成什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent.
It's gonna be set to what?
伊森: 三个。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Three.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 他说对了，数字是3。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He's spot on,
to num which evaluated to 3.
这就是标签，价值。
There it is, label, value.
在这里没什么不同。
No different to out here.
但是这些都有特殊的名字。
But these ones have special names.
这个叫做人的是什么？
What's this one known as people?
讲者2: 参数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Parameter.
威尔 · 森特斯: 这个呢，伙计们？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And this one here folks?
讲者2: 论点。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Argument.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 没错。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Exactly.
所以当函数结束时，占位符输入的数字将会被接收
So the placeholder input number that's
gonna receive when the function ends up
运行一个实际输入，实际值，实际数字。
being run an actual input,
actual value, actual number.
这个被传入的数字就是我们的论点。
That number that gets passed
in is known as our argument.
等待它的占位符称为我们的参数。
The placeholder that awaits
it is known as our parameter.
他们是完全不同的。
They are fundamentally different.
我指的是同一枚硬币的两面，但是
I mean that two sides of the same coin,
but
它们是完全不同的东西。
they are fundamentally different things.
一个是标签，一个是存储在标签里的东西。
One is the label,
one is the thing stored in that label.
好的，然后我们点击结果并分配它，伊森，什么？
Okay, then we hit result and
assign it, Ethan, what?
当它解决的时候也会有一个存储在里面吗？
When it's resolved gonna
also have a stored in it?
伊森: 输入数字乘以2。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Input number times two.
维尔 · 森坦斯: 哪一个会是？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is gonna be?
伊森: 六个 威尔 · 森特斯: 三乘二将会是
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Six.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Three by two is gonna be
6号，太好了，谢谢。
six, excellent, thank you.
对于伊森和最后的决赛来说，这是一场有趣的比赛。
To Ethan and
then the final it was an interesting one.
我们已经得到了丹，返回，实际上等待丹，我已经要求你很多时间。
We've got Dan, return, actually hold
on Dan, I've asked you lots of time.
所以我要把它混合起来，我要转向杰森。
So I'm going to mix it up,
I'm going to turn to Jason.
杰森，这最后一句话是什么意思？
Jason, what is this
final line saying here?
杰森: 意思是找到被绑定的内存块
&gt;&gt; Jason: It's saying that locate
the block of memory that is bound
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我喜欢。
to the label resolve and ship it out of-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, I like that.
我，好吧，你真的很喜欢。
I, all right, you really like that.
它说，去看看，这个词解决是什么意思？
It says, go look at,
what does this word resolve mean?
不会自动知道，所以它会在我们的本地内存中寻找它。
Javachip doesn't know automatically, so it
goes hunting for it in our local memory.
找到一个数字6，然后接受这个数字
Finds it's a number six and
then takes that number and
运输它返回它射出它。
ships it returns it shoots it out.
接下来会发生什么
What's literally gonna happen people
是因为运行调用做同样的事情很酷还是
is that the cool to the running of
the invocation doing the same thing or
乘以2等于3。
multiply by two and
number three is gonna evaluate to.
这意味着它会逐渐转化为,
That means it's gonna literally
turn into the value that,
人们看重的是这个，这里存储的任何东西。
people value is this this,
this the anything that's stored.
不是我们称之为标识符的标签,
Not the label,
which we fancy called the identifier,
就是存储为一个值的东西。
is the thing stored as a value.
我们要评估，也就是说我们要转动这个命令
We're going to evaluate, that is to
say we're going to turn this command
你不能存储到结果值中的东西
the thing you can't store
into the result value and
看，你要计算到数字6。
look at that is that you're going
to evaluate into the number six.
然后输出等于6
And then that output is equal to six and
就是这样，返回并分配到输出端。
there it is, returned out and
assigned to output.
我的天啊，好了，我们的执行线程。
My goodness.
All right, so our thread of execution.
因为在 JavaScript 中，有多少线程需要执行？
Wove in because by the way in JavaScript,
how many threads of execution?
就是这样，我想说我们一次能做多少事情，人们？
That's it, I'd say how many things
can we do at a time people?
我提出了两个不同的问题,
Well, I've asked two different
questions to pronounce is there,
我们有多少执行线程 Adam？
how many threads of
execution do we have Adam?
亚当: 只有一个。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Just one.
威尔: 一，这意味着我们一次做多少件事？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One, that means
how many things we do at a time?
同样的事情发生的可能性有多大。
What are the odds with the same.
好了，我们已经有了一个执行线程。
Okay, so
we have already one thread of execution.
一旦你想启动和执行一个函数，我们必须有一个线程编织
As soon as you want to start and execute
a function, we have to have a thread weave
然后开始运行这些代码行，然后它会迂回回来。
in and start running those lines of code
and then it's going to weave back out.
当我们运行这个函数时，我们不能继续在页面下方运行。
We can't continue on down the page
while we're running that function.
我们不能同时做两件事。
We don't do two things simultaneously.
我们将在明天的同步 JavaScript 中看到更多这方面的内容。
We're gonna see more about that with
a synchronous JavaScript to come tomorrow.
好吧，那么我们的执行线程就编织在里面了
All right, so
our thread of execution weaves in it then
我们在全球范围内碰到了什么线，不是吗，马克？
weaves back out with into global where
we hit what line, wasn't it Mark?
马克: 马克 威尔 · 森特斯: 马克,
&gt;&gt; Mark: Mark.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Mark,
对不起，马克，我们撞到什么线了，马克？
sorry Mark, we hit what line Mark?
标记: Const new output。
&gt;&gt; Mark: Const new output.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 宣布新的产出，就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Declaring new outputs,
there it is.
马克，我们知道怎么分配新的产出吗？
Mark, do we know what
to assign new output?
我们知道在新产品中存储什么了吗？
Do we know what to store
in new output yet?
马克: 没有 威尔 · 森坦斯: 因为我们要
&gt;&gt; Mark: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Because we gonna
去做什么？
go and do what?
马克: 我们必须创造另一个环境。
&gt;&gt; Mark: We have to
create another context.
句子: 执行上下文，我们要去执行什么功能马克？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context, we
gonna go and execute what function Mark?
马克: 乘以二。
&gt;&gt; Mark: Multiply by two.
威尔 · 桑特斯: 用？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: With the argument of?
马克: 10 威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了,
&gt;&gt; Mark: 10.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
我会督促马克尽可能完整地进行技术交流。
I'm gonna push Mark to be as complete as
possible with his technical communication.
这就是我们美丽的执行环境。
There it is,
there's our beautiful execution context.
比上一个好多了。
That's better than the last one.
然后我们进入它
And into it we go and
我知道这是难以置信的重复，这就是功能的本质。
I know this is incredibly repetitive,
well, that's the nature of function.
我们保存它一次，我们可以一次又一次地使用它，就是这样。
We save it once, we can use it again and
again, there we go.
进我们去输入数字大家，分配什么，我们的论点值多少？
Into we go and input number everybody, is
assigned what, our argument of the value?
马克: 10 威尔 · 森坦斯: 10,
&gt;&gt; Mark: 10.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 10,
做得好，结果是10乘以2得到20。
well done, and then result is
assigned 10 by two, which is 20.
然后，我们将结果的值返回到全局标记的新输出中。
Then we return the value of results
out into that global label new output.
就是这样，伙计们。
And there it is, people.
我的天啊，好吧。
My goodness, all right.
这是我们 JavaScript 平台三个部分中的两个核心部分。
That is the core two out of three
parts of our JavaScript platform.